apparently Amanda seals kind of came out
and was kind of thanking her loyal fans
about whatever whatever and then during
that she kind of you know was wondering
why she wasn't really accepted in Black
spaces or maybe boning the fact that she
was not and then um then there
apparently some articles came out one of
them by the Grio and other sources one
of them stuck out to me was a a sister
right who herself said she was loud it
can be whatever and was kind of giving
critique I think the name of the article
was Amanda seals is the victim of her
own Hubers or whatever right so a couple
of people also had their opinions or
whatever and then it was like the Amanda
seals Brigade stepped in right she did
interviews with different spots I heard
Mark Lon Hill and uh is that yeah is she
related to Jamal Hill because I felt
like both of them anyways right so
everybody certain people even the sister
in the parking lot you know what I mean
I forgot your name sis no disrespect um
kind of came to her Aid and I was
baffled by the conversation that was
being had